const items = [
    {
      activeKey: 0,
      question: "What subjects do you offer for learning?",
      answer: "We offer comprehensive training for HBO and IB in mathematics, physics, chemistry, biology, 3D modeling and printing, and languages. Our expert teachers cover a wide range of disciplines."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 1,
      question: "How are your teachers selected?",
      answer: "Our teachers are carefully chosen based on their experience, academic achievements, and teaching background. We ensure they are well-qualified to provide effective preparation for HBO and IB exams."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 2,
      question: "What is the class size for the training sessions?",
      answer: "We maintain individual classes to ensure personalized attention. This approach allows us to provide tailored support and focused learning."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 3,
      question: "How do you adapt your teaching to the individual needs of the student?",
      answer: "Our teachers understand each student's unique learning styles. We personalize our teaching approach to meet individual needs, offering targeted support and addressing specific challenges."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 4,
      question: "Can I choose the schedule for my lessons?",
      answer: "Yes, we offer flexible scheduling options. We work with students to find convenient time slots that fit their academic schedules and personal needs."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 5,
      question: "What resources do you provide for HBO and IB preparation?",
      answer: "We provide various resources including study materials, practice exams, and additional educational resources. Our goal is to equip students with the necessary tools for successful preparation for these important exams."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 6,
      question: "How do you track students' progress?",
      answer: "We regularly assess students' progress through assignments, tests, and periodic evaluations. This allows us to identify areas that need improvement and adjust our strategies accordingly."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 7,
      question: "What is your policy regarding missed sessions and courses?",
      answer: "We understand that unexpected events may occur, so we have a flexible makeup policy to ensure that students have the opportunity to cover missed material and stay on track with their learning."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 8,
      question: "How do I enroll in your training program?",
      answer: "To enroll, simply visit our website or contact our admissions team. We will guide you through the enrollment process and answer any additional questions you may have."
    },
    {
      activeKey: 9,
      question: "Are there any additional benefits or support services you offer to students?",
      answer: "In addition to our core training, we provide academic counseling, university application guidance, and support for extracurricular activities. We aim to ensure holistic support for our students' educational journey."
    }
  ];
  
  export default items;
  